Heat. Heat.
[music]
Hi guys, welcome to another weekly vlog.
As you can see by the title, we are
going to Barcelona.
I swear I feel like I'm probably the
most last minute person ever. Like any
of my friends, the moment they call me,
they're like, "You want to go?" I'm
like, "I'm down." Don't even mention a
trip because I'm already booking my
flight. Like, I'm already on my phone
like, "Okay, tell me what time and where
I'm going." But we're going to Barcelona
to celebrate Maya because she's the
birthday girl and we're basically gonna
have the best birthday weekend ever.
I've booked with two really nice
restaurants. So, yeah, I'm really
excited. It is currently 4:00 a.m. We've
been awake since 3:00 a.m. to go on this
trip. And don't ask me how I have
energy. I haven't slept at all the whole
night. So, I'm hoping to sleep on the
plane and then when I get to the beach,
take a huge nap while I'm tanning. But
yeah, this is literally me and Maya's
first trip and we've known each other
for like I don't know, seven, eight
years. So, I think it was finally time
for us to do it.
>> Ma will join post when we get to
Barcelona. [laughter]
>> Yeah, she's going to say hello when
she's ready.
>> Leave.
>> No, it's literally like 4:00 a.m. I
don't blame her. Made it to the airport.
>> Baby came.
>> Period. Okay, guys. So, we made it
through security. Now, we have like an
hour to waste. I'm so tired. Like I'm
starting to feel my energy going low, so
I can't wait to get on the plane and
sleep. First things first, I've never
had Jojo Juice at 4:00 a.m. in the
morning. But first time for everything.
Cheers. Birthday trip. It's the first
time I'm trying the Trust Sugar
smoothie. It has banana, strawberries,
and so many yummy things in it. M.
[music]
[music] So cute.
>> [music]
>> Barcelona will come. [music]
[bell]
We made it to Spain, guys.
We barely managed to even sleep on this
plane because it was freezing.
But we are making it work. I'm so happy.
Espanol [laughter]
may and I'm finally here. Got the
timelines already going. 48 hours in
Barcelona. Let's go. Let's get it.
[music]
So, we just checked in the hotel.
Unfortunately, we are too early. So,
packed our beach bags and we're going to
head straight to the beach. We changed
into a bikinis cuz we still have like 4
hours into check in. So, let's go. Guys,
it's my first [screaming]
complian.
>> Oh, for [\h__\h] sake. You just learned
that.
>> Look how pretty she looks, guys. By the
way, we literally got changed within 2
minutes.
>> 2 minutes. Our room's not ready, but
we're going to go to the beach. And what
kind of matchings? Yeah, we got the
white fit. [music]
>> So pretty. Day one in Barcelona.
Outfit of the day. I'm wearing this
beach cover up from Tiger Mist,
Australian brand with the little head
team.
Cute.
Okay.
We made it to the beach.
Oh, it feels so refreshing.
Oh, okay. Let me show you guys the room
tour.
It's so cute. We booked this literally
one day ago, but contemporary chic. This
is [music] the bathroom.
You have a direct [clears throat] view
to [music] the bedroom. And we asked for
two beds, so we're both really
comfortable. [music]
We got Dormon on the screen. Period.
It's cute for [music] two days. It's
cute, guys.
>> A I kind of like the city view, though.
>> Yeah, it's cute.
Careful.
We're breaking it. Setting up the vanity
space.
This is literally girlhood, guys. We
literally had the best time at the
beach. We went by the beach. We tan. It
felt so good. Um, and then now we're
back in the hotel getting ready for
dinner. I have these medicube eye
patches on. They're like my favorite
thing ever. Presenting you guys the
birthday girl.
>> What is it? Um, Phillies, I leave the
Spanish to you. Phillies, not [laughter]
neither
says it's my birthday.
>> Ooh.
>> Feeling old, but feeling [laughter]
>> wiser.
>> Let's not say my age.
>> She's 25.
>> Not 29, guys. Yeah. Let's just not
>> um
>> She's 25.
>> It's crazy because literally I met me
and Anna met at like 19.
>> We were 19 18 19. So, in university,
>> it's gone by so quickly.
>> It's crazy.
>> I feel like I'm not really in contact
with a lot of people from university. I
think you're like my top one or two
people. So,
>> he's done long distance. You've done
everything.
>> He's done everything.
>> So, we've come a long way, babes.
>> This trip was very much overdue and we
booked it so last minute,
>> literally 2 days before. [laughter] It's
crazy. But I feel like if anyone's down
for that, it's Anna.
>> She knows
>> best way to be. But we're here. It's
such nice weather. Anna's already said,
but we were swimming in the ocean,
>> tanning.
>> It just felt so, so good. [snorts]
>> I know. We're going for a little
birthday dinner. I don't know where it
is, but Anna's book somewhere.
>> It's a little surprise.
>> You know what? Nothing feels better than
like turning all day, swimming in the
ocean. Me and Maya were playing mermaids
and then um
>> salt water in our eyes.
>> Coming home to a nice cold fresh shower,
feeling tan and then getting ready for
dinner.
>> What's your one makeup essential?
>> Oh,
>> I feel like I could answer this, but I
feel like you're going to say something
different, but this is something I
always see you with.
>> Really?
>> An essential for me would be mascara.
>> I was going to say freckles.
>> Oh, really? Okay. Mascara, freckles.
>> We're going to have freckles today. If
you had to choose one makeup product.
Yeah.
>> Yeah.
>> To use like only one product to use like
for the rest of your life, what would it
be that you can use multi multi ways?
>> Do you know what is I love blush but one
thing about me guys the under eyes
[clears throat] are catching up with me.
So it' have to be concealer even though
I don't want it to be.
>> Just like one product would be
concealer.
>> I'd have to cuz I my eyes that's it. The
rest like an a lip gloss though.
>> I you know what my one product would be?
I'd say a lip stain cuz I feel like a
lip stain
>> I don't really use. I do use lip liners
for lip liner though. I love lipstick.
>> No, but you know why a lip stain is
good? Because you can use it on your
lips. You can create a little eye shadow
or you can create like a little blush.
>> Oh yeah, true.
>> And it'll stay on your face like the
whole day.
>> So, so far, how are you finding B? This
is Anna's first time in Barcelona.
>> I'm loving it. Really? I feel like I'm
really surprised. I feel like it's
giving like mountains, ocean.
>> One thing I'll say, everyone is so
chill. Yeah. So chill.
>> So chill.
>> I was not expecting this. I feel like
people that live in Barcelona probably
have such a good life.
>> This is a place where their life
expectancy is quite high.
>> Really?
>> Cuz you know like when you you live in
places where it's chill, where it's
calm,
>> Yeah.
>> you have a higher life expectancy.
>> What was the biggest lesson that you
learned this year?
>> So when I was younger, I used to be
really anxious about a lot of things
>> and I feel like that out of your
control. I feel like you shouldn't
stress about things. most of the time
like stressing about things, they don't
actually come to fruition. I feel like
you should spend that energy on positive
thinking. Not that you can't be down
about things, but I feel like life goes
on,
>> it always goes on. So, you kind of have
to learn to pick yourself up and learn
to be frame things positively. Like, you
know how we were talking about today,
the guy that scammed us and took us on a
walk,
>> we were like, well, we got 10k steps in,
so
>> Exactly. We're like, at least we got our
steps in to go back and forth. It
doesn't matter. You know,
>> I feel like life's too short to always
see the negative. Try and frame
positively [snorts] and try not to
stress because nothing is that deep. I
feel like most people
>> I love that cuz even me and Maya were in
the ocean today like literally floating
and manifesting and talking to the
universe about how grateful we are that
we are healthy that we have like our
family's healthy
>> and that's why I say nothing is that
deep because until you your health
that's something to like
>> I think my lesson this year would be
letting go and I feel like I've learned
how to do like discernment learn
discernment this year where Nothing is
really that deep for me. Like you said,
like people come, people go, friendship
comes, friendship go. And it's one of
those where I feel like sometimes people
come into your life. And in Vietnamese,
we have this thing called zuen, which is
basically faith. And like maybe you've
met them in the past life and you have
to meet them again this life so you can
repay each other's debt. Do
>> you know what I mean? Like if they
helped you out last like in the past
life, then you kind of help them out
this life. And once the debt has been
paid, then you go your separate ways.
And it's the same with like marriage and
kids and wife and husband and friends.
Like you don't just randomly cross path
with people.
>> No, I I'm a big believer in like people
can be in your life for seasons. But
that doesn't mean like you have to look
at it like oh my gosh, like I regret
that. Like they came and they taught you
a lesson or like you learned something
from it. So it's not
>> Yeah. Exactly. And I think I've really
mastered that this year. I'm just like
okay next.
We keep it stepping, you know. It's
never that deep. As long as you got your
family,
>> a few good friends, you're good. But
girl, we've been getting deep up in
here.
>> Yeah. No, literally. Should we play some
music?
>> Yeah. [singing]
Girl, I love you.
[singing]
[music]
>> [singing and music]
>> Okay guys, outfit of the night. If you
guys didn't know, Barcelona is known for
their gothic whimsical architecture. So,
I kind of wanted to go for that type of
vibe. This skirt I thrifted from Brick
Lane. My heels are from ASOS. This bag
TK Maxx I think. And then this top is
from Wet Avocado. It's a Vietnamese
brand. And obviously we got the jewelry.
Yep. The hair, the earrings.
[music]
>> Hi guys. Hey guys. So, me and Maya got
ready so quick and was so proud of
herself. We were actually like earlier.
Yeah, even [clears throat] earlier. But
look how beautiful my birthday girl
looks. Stunning. I'll show you guys her
full fit when we get out the car. But
right now, we are on the way to go to
Los Caracles, which is literally 6,000
reviews, 4.5 stars on Google, and it's
actually one of the oldest restaurants
in Barcelona. And it has literally been
around for 200 years. So, we are so
excited
>> for some good food because we've
literally been fasting all day.
>> Not that we were fasting on purpose, but
honestly, we just wanted to go to the
beach and chill and
>> we forgot about food.
>> Yeah, we just forgot about food.
Honestly, got our 10k steps in. So
productive. Had only 2 hours sleep.
>> But we're making it here.
>> I'm going to have a good time. I'm going
to eat some really good food.
>> Yes. So excited.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Hey,
hey, hey.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Birthday girl. What is your fit? Um, is
it just ASOS? [laughter]
>> ASOS.
>> Face car. Thank you.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Guys, we're running so late for the
dinner,
but we're making it. O caracolis 200y
old establishment.
>> Wow.
>> With the history facts.
>> Look at this. The rositerary chicken is
crazy.
Open fire.
Guys, look at that.
All of the ham that's hanging.
>> Insane.
And then there's usually people having a
whole dinner downstairs.
Love that the whole theme is like
literally snails because they are known
for one of their best dishes.
Guys, so we got the ham. Look how
beautiful this looks. Thinly sliced.
We've got the grilled octopus.
Yum.
And then we've got the prawns.
The shrimp is so crispy and delicious.
You can just tell it's just so well
seasoned.
>> Octopus.
I think they put like parts of it on top
of the the and it's just the way it
melts in your mouth and the flavors.
I'm not even you can taste the fresh
fruit, babe. This with some cheese and
some grapes.
If I had to rate it, octopus number one,
>> ham number two, shrimp number three,
shrimp number one for sure. Octopus
number
three.
>> I'm such a ham girl, though. So, this
restaurant is literally named after
their iconic dish, which is this is the
snails. I can't wait to try it.
>> To eat so little and then cheers.
And I'm trying, but this is a stretch
for me and go.
>> There's nothing.
>> Oh my god.
Hell no, man. What the [\h__\h]
>> Not going to lie, I'm kind of
disappointed by the snails cuz I feel
like I was expecting a different flavor,
but the flavor is very much like a meat
seasoning. So, but everything else was
so delicious. I think I prefer the
French esto comparing to this. So, we
got their famous roasted chicken as you
guys saw earlier. We got some grilled
veggies and some sides, potatoes. The
sangria is getting to me.
>> Thank you.
[cheering] Thank you.
that restaurant. I give it a good 7.5/8
because I feel like the chicken was a
tiny bit salty and then I didn't love
the snails which they were famous for.
So,
>> good choice though.
>> Sri.
>> Yeah. And do you know what the vibe of
it is very
>> it's a company company 10 cent.
>> Yeah.
>> Spain at night.
I think he drunk. [music]
[music]
Good morning world.
This is the view that we are waking up
to.
So gorgeous. We are such productive
queens. It is currently 9:00 a.m. and we
are going to the gym.
Because why not? Keep in shape while on
vacation.
>> Oh, they have a stair master.
Oh, okay. It's just this one,
some arm. We got weights over here.
Don't Don't look at my mech bag, guys. I
have no bags, so we making it work.
>> And then I love a view when you work
out.
>> Yeah, it motivates you. Hey, guys. I
just came back from the gym, showered. I
feel so fresh. Do you guys see the tan
lines?
I know. That's right. But today is going
to be a little solo day for me because
Maya wants to just kind of relax and
tan. So, I'm going to let her. I
actually want to go and explore
Barcelona and do some vintage shopping.
I want to go and see Sagada Familia just
like from the outside. I don't really
need to go inside cuz I don't think I
have enough time to do that in the day.
And then later on when I come back, we
have a really nice dinner reservation
that I booked. Today I want to kind of
try try out the Naked Sundays um SPF
like mineral stick peptide. So it's kind
of giving bronzer but it's like SPF in
it. Okay. I was going to say guys
honestly Barcelona is so charming. is so
pretty, charming. I love the
architecture.
So, I cannot wait to go and explore more
of it today. I'm literally just going to
do the most sun-kissed natural makeup,
no foundation, like no concealer,
nothing. Just blush, bronzer, little
freckles, and then call it a day because
it's going to be 32° outside today. So,
it's hot.
[music]
>> [music]
>> But yeah, so this is my daytime natural
makeup. So makeup is done. [music] Let's
do our hair and get dressed. Okay, guys.
This is the outfit of the day. This set
is from Kai Collective. I'm obsessed
with the gold detailing [music] for you
guys. How cute is this?
Got the jewelry.
Pair the whole outfit
with my little mini yellow Chanel.
I think it's so cute.
And because we are going to be walking
basically the whole day, I'm wearing my
Vibrams. Let's go, guys. First solo day
out. I'm so excited. I love doing things
by myself because I feel like you get to
really beat social anxiety and you just
get to explore and take time for
everything you want to do.
>> Guys, we made it. Sra Familia. So
pretty.
The architecture is insane.
Like it literally looks like Hotel
Transylvania. So I basically did my
research and I learned that the
construction of the Sagrada Familia
actually started in the 80s by Francisco
de Paula and then it got taken over by
Anthony Gaudi who was the one that
introduced the Gothic style that got so
famous around the world because it's so
cool. It's like gothic whimsical like
new. He just mixed all the SS and Gaudi
actually died because he got struck by a
tram and then they ended up burying him
in one of the chapels inside the
Sagradia Familia. So yeah, I guess like
who needs a tour guide? I can literally
give you guys the facts. I'mma be my own
tour guide. So pretty.
This [music] whole area is so pretty,
guys.
[music]
It feels like it's almost like candle
wax like falling down. I literally love
this so much. Literally boiling outside.
It's like 32°. I was literally sweating
my pants off. I'm glad I got to see the
Sagrada Familia and just see the
architecture and the history behind it
all. But now the fun part starts because
we are going shopping because today is
actually Sunday. So, I had no idea that
the shops open at 12:00 p.m. and then
some shops even open at 2:00 p.m. So,
I'm actually quite early. So, let's go
check out some shops and then walk
around.
>> [music]
>> The store is so pretty.
These are so cute.
I love how colorful everything is.
Definitely want to try on some stuff.
It's kind of like elevated basics. Look
at this bikini.
She's colorful.
How cute are these ballerina flats? Like
they just look so comfortable. I feel
like I'm so like late to the ballerina
trend, but I love my Vibrams. So, I
guess it's time for me to try out the
ballerinas and see how I feel about
them.
What do we think?
Life is literally all about beating
social anxiety. Look, I just met like a
new friend. She's been taking the
bombest pictures for me and helping me
choose a pair of ballerina blades.
>> Say hi.
>> Yeah. Hi.
>> What's your name?
>> Yeah. My name is Siana. [laughter]
>> Right. Here it is. She's from Mongolia.
Asian baddies in the building. So, I
just tried on this purple top. I just
love the detailing on it. But I don't
know if I like the way it sits. Maybe I
need to wear something like tighten it.
It's kind of giving Vietnamese in a way.
Like I am. I've decided to go for this
gray pair. My first pair of ballerinas.
You can literally [music] wear it with
white, black, any color. And they don't
get as dirty as the white.
Goodies secured,
guys. First goodie secured. I am now on
my way to the next stop, which is the
vintage shopping.
>> [music]
>> The architecture is so pretty here.
Everything is just so unique.
[music]
>> [music]
>> This is the second stop of the day. It's
called Near Vintage.
I'm so excited to see what they have. My
first time in um Barcelona.
>> Okay, welcome to N. Everything you see
is pick vintage items, but we focus on
trends.
[music]
>> [music]
>> So, I didn't end up liking anything from
near vintage. And then the other shop
that I really wanted to visit was it's
called Busy [\h__\h] but it's not open. I
didn't realize that it's not open until
Monday. So, there's only one more shop
that I really want to check out, which
is Lemon Studios. Um, it's 16 minute
walk for me. So, I'm literally just
going to walk there. But maybe let's get
some matcha or some refreshment before.
Nori matcha.
[music]
No drama. Just matcha. Let's do a little
taste test.
M
>> I can tell that the blueberry is very
much fresh. I love these little street
mirrors. How cute.
You look good.
>> Thank you, girl. Matcha and shopping.
It calls for a perfect day. I literally
love just walking around and just seeing
different areas. Having solo time is so
important and so fun because you just
get to explore. I met like five people
today. I've just been asking different
people to take pictures for me. Maybe I
need to try out solo traveling. That's
one thing I've never done. So Barcelona
is kind of pushing me to kind of get
into that. And I love it. Like look at
all the streets.
It's like a mix of French, Italian.
[music and singing]
[music]
So this is the cathedral of Barcelona.
How beautiful is this? [music]
>> [music]
[music]
>> This is so stunning. [singing]
It's every other road. I'm [music] like
gas. I feel like I'm in some medieval
town.
>> [music]
>> I think I'm obsessed with Spain, guys.
So, guys, I think I stumbled on a really
cool concept store as well. I think they
carry like different brands.
Guys, I found this cutest necklace.
How unique is this?
Would just elevate the outfit.
Right. This is so unique.
[music]
>> They literally even have Korean skin
care here.
Some bikinis. [music]
You know what I really like about them?
They have these really cool [music] like
sheer tops.
And then now for the store that we've
been wanting to find, Lemon Studios.
Wait, how cute is this store? I'm
already seeing Cavali from far. [music]
Now, this is more my type of vibe.
I
>> think there's some John Po goier up in
here. Shades Gucci.
>> Got the vintage Chanel.
>> Doesn't fit my nose like always.
>> I like the brown. [music]
And this is funny.
I like these, but I feel like I have too
many black [music] shades. What are we
thinking?
>> Guys, how cute is this store?
We got vintage DNG here. I love it. I
think I could wear this with a little
black bralette inside. It's just cabali.
Then he brought out these little Dior
heels.
It's kind of giving wooden a 350.
>> What's your name?
>> I'm finally back in the hotel and I've
had the best best time solo shopping,
exploring the town, seeing like
architectural monuments. And then now
that I'm back, I'm going to go and lay
down, tan, swim. Honestly, this is the
most perfect day. 20k steps, a good ass
matcha, and vintage shopping. What else
could a girl want? Guys, we made it back
to the beach. I'm with Maya right now
and we have a good an hour and a half,
two hours to tan and enjoy the ocean
before we go back and get ready for
dinner. But I think I've had a very
productive day
bikini of the day. I'm going for this
army. I think it's from Body Source.
Guys, it's our last night in Barcelona.
Short but sweet.
>> Short was very, very sweet. I think
we've literally had the best time. We
are on our way to the last restaurant.
Like, I've seen all the reviews, so I
can't wait to try it. And there's going
to be like a performance, but we still
have the whole day tomorrow.
>> Yeah.
>> So, we're planning to go to the beach,
get a walk, wake up early.
>> Yep. Get our steps in, check out, and
then honestly just have the best time.
You have fun yesterday for your
birthday.
>> So fun. Anna actually want me to eat
now. I can't believe it. from a
[laughter] time. But other than that,
there's a memory here forever that
you're going to remember.
>> Outfit of the night. I'm wearing this
dress from Tigerness. I love how it's
like a little gold necklace holding it.
On this backless,
we got the ASOS heels, Maya's bag, and
then
some real pretty red earrings to go with
the fit. This is Maya's outfit. I got
the bag and this bag which today.
>> How pretty.
>> From Zara skirt.
>> Stunning thing from Zara too. And then
this top is from Zara. Actually whole
outfit from Zara.
>> Period. Oh my god. So pretty.
>> [music]
>> Guys, so this is our dinner spot.
Anna
Cheers, guys.
>> We should have been downstairs, but God
has a plan for everything.
>> It's very cute. I feel like this is
dinner, though.
>> Yeah.
[music]
Look at the scallop. Looks beautiful.
And then we got some red shrimp tata as
well. [music] Yummy.
Cheers.
[music]
>> Yeah. Beautiful.
Super.
[music]
Guys, I'm going to be real. Yesterday's
restaurant was [music] like so much
better than this place. This place has
higher reviews, but I guess you can't
really trust the reviews online. The
lamb is so unseasoned. The pasta is just
not the best I've ever had. The best
I've ever had was the meos. Gallup was
also like there's just like very fishy
season.
>> I feel like every dish there's just
something that's missing. Yeah, it's
missing and it's like not elevated. It's
like just very like it feels like they
cook everything very safe. Like there's
no experimental. There's some flavors
that blows my mind, you know?
>> Yeah. But maybe we're just being picky.
Even Salt and Pepper is not open this.
>> Okay, guys. I think I would give that
restaurant a five out of 10. Not
>> Not to be dramatic. What would you give
it? Five.
>> I feel like it lacked seasoning. We like
seasoning. Not overpowering, but it I
feel like it had nothing ate nothing. It
was just there's something lacking on
every single dish which is so weird. How
do you not make grilled scallops? Bomb.
It's the easiest thing to make.
>> Nothing. I feel like they just slapped
some tomato on it and that was it. And
they put like butter but no garlic
butter.
>> Now we are on a little walk exploring
the neighborhood. It's our last night. I
love how they put the mopets like in the
middle of the road.
>> Me and Maya are trying to convince
herself not to get any
>> Yeah. No sweet ice cream. Maybe
tomorrow.
Not her walking off.
>> Now, now walk off.
>> Now walk off.
>> And that was it, guys. We are in and
out. So, we are now about to check out
and go to the beach. We have a few hours
to enjoy and then on the plane back to
London. I think I've had this jersey top
since like I don't know 2 3 years now.
And I've just been waiting until the day
I go to Barcelona. an inkling that I
will be here one day to wear and rep
Barcelona. Now we're heading towards the
beach. Try to have the best paella right
before the plane. So, uh, we done a
little research. So, let's hope the food
is actually better than last night.
[music]
It was so funny, guys. [music] We were
in the Uber and then I was like speaking
Spanish, my little broken Spanish that I
know. And I was like,
[laughter]
[gasps] and then he was like, "Oh, do
you speak Spanish?" And I was like,
"Pito, I'm glad we were going to this
area towards the uh end of the trip.
Even the beach looks nicer."
Ocean
so pretty.
I don't know. Hey,
[music]
I think me and Maya had the best time at
the beach today. We tanned for like
literally 3 hours and then we went to
take a shower at like you know them
outdoors shower pose and it felt so
good. Then now Maya's getting herself a
little sangria and then we're going to
this restaurant that's really known for
their pellas and then have some good
lunch and then we're going to head back
to the hotel and get ready for the
airport.
>> [music]
>> We got us a sangria. Mandatory.
>> Guys, this pella is huge. Look at my
hand. Wo, that is huge. How are we going
to finish this as two people? We got the
paella with the shells. This pella is
probably one of the best that I've had.
It's so delicious. And I put some tobaso
on top.
The tabasco
topping it. [music]
We got the grilled octopus and it looks
divine.
I hope. But yeah, guys, that was it for
this Barcelona vlog. I hope you guys
enjoyed it as much as I did because we
lived it up. Like we literally lived our
best life. It was so fun. We were at the
beach every day. As you guys can see,
your girl has tan and we ate really,
really good food. And the pa today was
literally the cherry on top. The only
thing was like we've never ever been
like tipsy to go to the airport before,
right? So we were drinking the sangria
at brunch and we were like, "Yo, this
sangria is so strong, but it was so
yummy." So we kept drinking it and then
we were like, "Okay, perfect. We're
going to get on the plane. We're going
to take a nap and we're going to
basically space out. Ask me why.
We are currently sitting down after we
have already missed our first flight.
So, we get to the airport. We did a
great timing, but as we were standing in
the check-in line, we didn't realize how
much time has passed because the line
was going so slow. So, then we went to
the emergency line to check in and then
they were like, "Well, the gates been
closed. It's it closes 1 hour before."
And I was like, I have never heard of a
gate closing an hour before. So, long
story short, we missed our flight. We
were literally running back and forth
trying to go through security, so many
things. And then in the end, we
literally just had to book a new flight.
So, our flight's been delayed like an
hour. But, woof, I guess this is my my
lesson. Like, first and last time ever
getting tipsy before a flight. Like,
just no drinking for me in general.
Like, I don't think it it's I'm made for
that. And today was just so stressful.
Like honestly, the whole trip was
amazing. And then just this was like the
only setback we've had the whole trip.
But other than that, [laughter]
Maya was crying.
>> I've never missed a flight. I've seen so
many flights. I've never missed one.
>> It's just too stressful.
>> It's fun to tell the children,
>> but at least it's like a memory for the
book later on.
>> But yeah, guys, like always, if you like
this video, what do you do? Like and
subscribe.
>> Like, subscribe, and comment. And make
sure you hyped up the video.
>> Get to 50K.
>> Yeah, get me to 50K.
But yeah, I love you guys. And always
find the positive in the negative,
right? And I will see you in the next
video. Mwah.